How did viewing a diff between two versions help see the bug?

diff/fc compare text files on a line by line basis.
Thus you are only shown the lines that have changed.
You need to go through all those lines manually and try to detect a mistake.

------------------------------------------------
How could having easy access to the entire history of a file make you a more efficient programmer in the long term?
- see progress over time
- revert to bugfree version if necessary
- find bugs/error in the code
- use "template" states for future projects
- see who made which changes
- correlate changes with problem reports/complaints

------------------------------------------------
What do you think are the pros and cons of manually choosing when to create a commit, like you do in Git, vs having versions automatically saved, like Google Docs does?

Pros of manual saving
- commits represent logical changes rather than time changes. The commit message clearly states what has changed
- allows forking/branching of a project
- only create the number of versions necessary, not less

Cons of manual saving
- forgetfulness!
- 

------------------------------------------------
Why do you think some version control systems, like Git, allow saving multiple files in one commit, while others, like Google Docs, treat each file separately?

- because some logical changes require several files to be updated at once
- files are interrelated


------------------------------------------------
How can you use the commands git log and git diff to view the history of files?
- git log shows the history of commits (changes)
- git diff <commit1> <commit2> will show you all files that have changed
- git diff displays each line that was removed or added for each file affected


------------------------------------------------
How might using version control make you more confident to make changes that could break something?
- can always revert to a safe (aka working) state of the code
- can make incremental changes to code and find the exact change that introduced a bug

------------------------------------------------
Now that you have your workspace set up, what do you want to try using Git for?
- I want to use git to modify and branch the examples provided in "Learning Processing" 
- It's learning by doing really!

